Hi, my name is Carsten Gaki and I'm a product manager at Figure Eight.
大家好 我是 Carsten Gaki 我是 Figure Eight 的产品经理
Where I work with a team that builds products to solve
在公司 我与团队合作 打造产品来解决数据标签问题
data labeling problems frequently encountered in the machine learning space.
数据标签问题是机器学习领域的常见问题
In this lesson, I'll be discussing the importance of data and machine
在本课里 我将讨论数据和机器学习的重要性
learning and how to create a high-quality training data-set.
以及如何创建高质量训练数据集
In the last lesson, you learned that a good Product Manager will know a lot
在上节课里 我们学习了一个好的产品经理应该对产品了如指掌
about their product and how it might be improved with machine learning techniques.
包括 如何通过机器学习技术来改进产品
Machine learning relies on having a relevant and large enough data source.
机器学习依赖于一个相关性强的、体量大的数据来源
So, how do we go about answering questions using data?
那么 我们如何使用数据来解决问题呢？
Say you're a Product Manager for
假设 你是一家在线零售商的产品经理
an online retailer and you're tasked with improving search results.
你的任务是改进搜索结果
What exactly does that mean?
这是什么意思呢？
Well, it could mean that if a user searches for a pair of pants,
比如 如果一个用户搜索裤子
they always get back irrelevant result.
他们应该可以得到相关结果
One that matches their query closely.
一个非常匹配他们搜索的结果
It could also mean that this experience is tailored to a user.
这也可以意味着 搜索结果是个性化的
If they're told you something about their preferred style or fit,
如果他们曾经告诉过你 他们偏好的风格或者尺寸
you could show those kinds of pant options early on.
你就可以在一开始就展示这些类别的裤子选项
This idea may be more promising but it's also more difficult in certain cases.
这也许是可以实现的 但是在某些情况下 也非常难以实现
Like if someone's a new user and you don't yet know their preferences.
比如 如果对方是一个新用户 你暂时还不知道他们的喜好
You need data to make both of these improvements work.
对于以上提到的两种方案 你都需要用到数据
In the first case, you'll need data about the relevancy of certain search items,
在第一个方案里 你需要关于某些搜索商品的相关性的数据
and in the second case you'll need data about individual preference.
在第二个方案里 你需要用户的个人喜好数据
When you start to narrow down a business question like this,
当你开始像这样缩小业务问题的范围时
you intuitively start thinking about what information
你会不由自主地开始思考 如果要达成这项任务
will actually be most useful in solving this task.
哪些数据或者信息是最有用的
In this lesson, we'll discuss how you can build
在这节课 我们将讨论如何基于一个特定的业务问题
a data-set with the business problem in mind.
来创建一个数据集
We'll address identifying data fit,
我们会讨论数据的适用性
and how well a data-set matches a problem,
数据集与业务问题的匹配程度
determining whether a data-set is complete and if it contains
判断一个数据集是否完整 以及它是否包含了
enough information to represent all real world use cases,
现实生活里所有使用场景的例子
and finally, we'll spend the bulk of this lesson discussing methods for data labeling,
最后 本课的重点内容是教授给数据打标签的不同方法
also known as data annotation.
也称为 数据标注
Specifically we'll go over an example of building a data-set for
然后 我们将学习一个具体示例 即 使用 Figure Eight 数据标注平台
traffic sign classification using figure eights data annotation platform.
为交通信号灯分类模型构建数据集
At each of these steps will also address strategies for
在每一个步骤 我们也会讲到如何确保
ensuring the quality of your data and the user experience over time.
数据质量和良好的用户体验的策略
By the end of this lesson, you should have all the information you
在本课的结尾 你应该具备了独立完成数据标注项目的所有知识